it turns out there are several different
原来有几种不同的
ways to define Bayesian games this video
视频定义贝叶斯游戏的方法
is going to give the first definition so
将给出第一个定义，所以
before thinking about Bayesian games
在考虑贝叶斯游戏之前
everything we've thought about has
我们所考虑的一切都有
assumed that all of the players know
假设所有玩家都知道
what game is being played that is
正在玩什么游戏
everybody knows how many players there
每个人都知道那里有多少球员
are in the world what actions are
在世界上什么是行动
available to every player and what
每个玩家可用的内容
payoffs would result given a complete
如果得到完整的回报
action profile or an action vector by
动作配置文件或动作向量
everybody so let me give you a chance to
大家，让我给你一个机会
stop and think about why this is still
停下来想一想为什么仍然如此
true and imperfect information games
真实和不完美的信息游戏
because intuitively it might seem to you
因为从直觉上看来
like it isn't true so you might want to
就像那不是真的，所以你可能想
pause the video now and think about that
现在暂停视频并考虑一下
and then I'll tell you the answer so the
然后我会告诉你答案，所以
reason why imperfect information games
信息游戏不完善的原因
still have all of these things being
仍然拥有所有这些东西
true is that what you don't remember in
的确是你不记得的
an imperfect information game is what
不完美的信息游戏是什么
actions other players have played at the
其他玩家在
moment when you're about to take your
当你即将拿走你的时刻
own action but it's still the case that
自己的行动，但事实仍然如此
you know what actions are available to
你知道可以采取哪些行动
everybody and it's still the case that
大家，现在仍然如此
if you know what everybody fully did a
如果你知道每个人都做了什么
complete action profile by everybody
大家完整的动作简介
what payoff would result now we want to
现在我们想要得到什么回报
think about games where these
想想这些游戏
assumptions aren't true anymore
假设不再正确
so what we are still going to make some
所以我们仍然要做一些
new assumption so let me tell you about
新的假设，让我告诉您
that so what we're relaxing is that all
所以我们放松的是
players know what game is being played
玩家知道正在玩什么游戏
so we're now going to think about the
所以我们现在要考虑
idea that there's more than one possible
有不止一种可能性的想法
game that the players can think about
玩家可以考虑的游戏
and among all of these possible games
在所有这些可能的游戏中
that the players will reason about
玩家会思考的
they're all going to be games that have
他们都将成为具有
the same number of agents and the same
相同数量的代理商和相同
strategy space for each agent so how
每个代理商的战略空间如何
they're going to be different is just in
他们将会与众不同
the utility functions and that's
实用程序功能，那就是
important because it's just difficult to
重要，因为这很难
model a situation where you're not quite
模拟一个您不太满意的情况
sure what strategy space you have it
确定您拥有什么策略空间
would
将
be clear how to act now you might find
清楚现在该如何行动
it useful to reason about games in which
对其中的游戏进行推理很有用
you're not sure what other agents there
您不确定那里还有其他代理商
are turns out that's actually possible
事实证明这实际上是可能的
to capture within this framework in that
在这个框架内捕获
case you would just always believe that
如果你只是一直相信
the maximum number of agents were
代理商人数最多
present in every game but you'd set up
出现在每款游戏中，但您需要进行设置
the utility functions in a way where
该实用程序的运行方式
sometimes it doesn't matter that some of
有时候，
the agents are present because they're
代理商在场是因为他们
not able to affect anything the second
不能影响第二
assumption that we're going to make it
假设我们要做到
has to do with the beliefs that agents
与代理商的信念有关
have about these different possible
有这些不同的可能
games so in order for this to work it
游戏，以便使它起作用
has to be the case that agents still
必须是代理商仍然
have well-defined beliefs about what is
对什么有明确的信念
possible in the world and we're going to
世界上有可能，我们将
say that the agents start out with a
说代理商开始于
common prior so that is everyone has the
共同的先验，所以每个人都有
same beliefs about what it is that's
关于那是什么的相同信念
possible in the world what what games it
世界上可能有什么游戏
is that that are possible and then they
那是可能的，然后他们
might get individual private information
可能会获得个人私人信息
about in fact what game is being played
关于实际上正在玩什么游戏
and then they'll do Bayesian updating so
然后他们将进行贝叶斯更新
they'll end up with a posterior belief
他们最终会后悔
which is obtained by starting from this
从此开始获得
common prior and updating it based on
共同的先验并根据
their private information so that's an
他们的私人信息，所以
assumption we could believe that the
假设我们可以相信
agents had different prior beliefs but
特工有不同的先验信念，但
but that's not what we assume in the
但这不是我们在
case of Bayesian games so here's one
贝叶斯游戏的情况，这是一个
definition of Bayesian games in terms of
贝叶斯游戏的定义
information sets so a Bayesian game is a
信息集，所以贝叶斯游戏是
set of games that differ only in their
一组仅在其方面有所不同的游戏
payoffs also a common prior defined over
收益也是在
these games and a partition structure
这些游戏和分区结构
over the games for each agent so in
在每个代理商的游戏中
other words a Bayesian game is defined
换句话说，定义了贝叶斯博弈
by four elements the first is a set of
通过四个元素，第一个是一组
agents the second is a set of games
代理商第二套游戏
recall that a game is defined as a set
回想一下，游戏被定义为一组
of agents a set of action profiles sorry
特工的一套行动资料对不起
a set of action sets one for each agent
一组操作为每个代理设置一个
and a set of utility functions one for
以及一组用于
each agent
每个代理
so we're gonna restrict this set of
所以我们要限制这套
games here to all have in common the
这里的游戏都有共同点
same set of agents and also the same
同一组代理人，也相同
action sets so these games are going to
动作设定，因此这些游戏将
differ only in their utility functions
仅在实用功能上有所不同
then P is going to be an element of the
那么P将成为
set of all possible probability
所有可能概率的集合
distributions over games this is going
通过游戏进行发行
to be our prior distribution so this is
成为我们之前的发行，所以这是
going to tell us how likely each of
告诉我们每个
these games from the set G is and
这些来自集合G的游戏是和
finally we're going to have a set of
最终我们将有一套
partitions of g1 for each agent so this
每个代理的g1分区，因此
is going to be a set of equivalence
将是一组等价的
classes that will say from the point of
从这个角度讲的课程
view of an agent certain games are
代理商的观点某些游戏是
indistinguishable from each other and
彼此无法区分
others are not let's look at an example
别人不让我们看一个例子
so this example is a little bit
所以这个例子有点
contrived ordinarily we're gonna use
通常，我们会使用
Bayesian games to model something that
贝叶斯游戏为模型建模
that kind of makes some sort of sense in
这种感觉在某种意义上
the world then here really where we're
那么这个世界真的在这里
looking at something kind of artificial
看着某种人造的东西
but it's a small example that still lets
但这是一个小例子，仍然可以
us think about everything important
我们考虑所有重要的事情
about a Bayesian game so the first thing
关于贝叶斯游戏，所以第一件事
to notice is that there are four
注意，有四个
possible games that might be played
可能玩的游戏
matching pennies prisoner's dilemma
匹配便士囚徒困境
coordination or battle of the sexes
男女的协调或战斗
incidentally prisoner's dilemma here is
顺带一提，囚徒的困境是
being played with different payoffs than
所获得的收益与
you might have seen before but that
您可能以前见过，但是
doesn't matter it's strategically the
没关系，从战略上讲
same game and we have a common prior
相同的游戏，我们有一个共同的先验
over the games so there's a 30% chance
在游戏中，因此有30％的机会
that the game that the players will in
玩家将参与的游戏
fact be playing is matching pennies
事实是打出了几分钱
there's a 10% chance that they will in
他们有10％的机会会参加
fact be playing prisoner's dilemma 20%
事实是犯人的困境20％
chance of coordination and 40% chance of
协调的机会和40％的机会
battle of the sexes now haven't marked
性别之战现在还没有标记
the actions in these games but our
这些游戏中的动作，但我们的
assumption is that they have to be the
假设他们必须是
same so let's say player 1 has two
一样，假设玩家1有两个
choices top or bottom he gets to choose
他可以选择的顶部或底部
the top or bottom action and it's the
顶部或底部的动作，这是
same every game and likewise player two
每个游戏都一样，两个玩家也一样
can choose left or right and he gets the
可以选择左或右，他得到
left or right action in each game
每个游戏中的向左或向右动作
so what is interesting here of course is
所以这里有趣的是
that we have these information sets so
我们有这些信息集
player one how it gets to find out which
玩家之一如何找到哪个
of these two sets the game is in what
在这两套游戏中，
that means is in fact nature is going to
这意味着事实上大自然将会
decide which game gets played so
决定玩什么游戏
randomly it's going to be decided which
随机决定
of the four games being played according
在四场比赛中，
to the common prior let's say the most
可以说是最常见的事
likely thing happens and the players end
可能发生的事情，玩家结束了
up playing battle of the sexes in that
在那玩两性之战
case what player one is going to find
案例一个玩家会找到什么
out is that he's in this equivalence
就是他在这等价
class rather than this one so that means
类而不是这一类，这意味着
he's gonna know for sure that he's not
他会确定他不是
playing matching pennies or prisoner's
玩匹配的便士或囚犯的
dilemma but he's gonna think that he
困境，但他会认为他
might be playing either coordination or
可能正在协调或
battle of the sexes he's gonna have no
他将没有性别之战
way of telling them apart now player two
区分他们的方式现在是玩家2
has different equivalence classes so
具有不同的等效类
player two considers these two games to
玩家二认为这两场比赛
be indistinguishable and likewise
难以区别
considers these two games to be
认为这两个游戏是
indistinguishable and continuing our
难以区分并继续我们
example from before if this was really
如果真的是以前的例子
the game that was randomly chosen by
随机选择的游戏
nature then player two would find out
自然，然后第二个玩家会发现
that he was in this equivalence class
他在这个同等班上
rather than this one
而不是这个
meaning that he would think the game
意味着他会认为比赛
being played was either prisoner's
扮演囚犯的
dilemma or battle of the sexes and the
男女两难的困境或斗争
ground ground truth would be that in
基本事实是
fact battle of the sexes was being
性别之战正在
played he would consider it possible the
打他会认为这可能
prisoner's dilemma was being played and
囚徒的困境正在发挥，
we've already seen the player one would
我们已经看到了玩家会
consider it possible the coordination
认为有可能协调
was being played and what this means is
正在播放，这意味着
that when the players are deciding what
当玩家决定什么
what action to take they're gonna have
他们将采取什么行动
to play an action without fully knowing
在不完全了解的情况下进行动作
what game is going to be played and
将要玩什么游戏，以及
they're gonna have to reason about what
他们将不得不思考什么
their opponent is doing without fully
他们的对手没有完全做到
knowing what the opponent is going to
知道对手将要做什么
think they will they do know everything
认为他们会知道一切
about this setting so this whole kind of
关于这个设置，所以整个
picture is something that the players
画面是玩家所需要的
know they know the common prior they
知道他们先知道共同点
know their own equivalence classes and
知道自己的等效类
they know their opponent's equivalence
他们知道对手的当量
classes so if I'm player one and I want
上课，所以如果我是一名选手，我想
to reason about what player 2 is going
推断玩家2的前进方向
to do and I know that
去做，我知道
I'm in this equivalence class then I
我在这个同等班
also know that player 2 that if the game
也知道玩家2
is really coordination which I believe
我真的很协调
is possible then player 2 thinks he's in
可能然后玩家2认为他在
this equivalence class and thinks that
这个等价类，并认为
matching pennies is possible even though
匹配便士是可能的，即使
I know it's not possible
我知道不可能
or on the other hand if battle of the
或另一方面，如果
sexes is the real game that's being
性是真正的游戏
played then I know that player 2 thinks
玩过，然后我知道玩家2认为
he's in this equivalence class which
他在这个同等班
means he's gonna think prisoner's
表示他会认为囚犯的
dilemma as possible even though I know
即使我知道两难
it's not possible and I'll leave for a
这是不可能的，我会去一个
future video actually how we reason
未来的视频实际上我们是如何推理的
about these games but what we've learned
关于这些游戏，但我们学到了什么
here is how to define a Bayesian game by
这是如何通过定义贝叶斯游戏
writing it as a probability distribution
将其写为概率分布
a common probability distribution over
共同概率分布
multiple different normal form games all
多个不同的普通形式游戏
of which share the same number of
其中共享相同数量的
players and the same action sets
玩家和相同的动作集